[
  {
    "question": "What is the approximate length of the Great Barrier Reef in kilometers?",
    "answer": "2300",
    "providedAnswer": "1200",
    "timeTaken": 0,
    "totalTime": 81566
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the approximate length of the Great Barrier Reef in kilometers?",
    "answer": "2300",
    "providedAnswer": "1200",
    "timeTaken": 0,
    "totalTime": 12204
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the approximate length of the Great Barrier Reef in kilometers?",
    "answer": "2300",
    "providedAnswer": "1200",
    "timeTaken": 0,
    "totalTime": 136200
  },
  {
    "question": "How many times can a hummingbird's heart beat in one minute?",
    "answer": "1200",
    "providedAnswer": "1200",
    "timeTaken": 0,
    "totalTime": 4995
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the second largest land mammal?",
    "answer": "Rhinoceros",
    "providedAnswer": "1200",
    "timeTaken": 0,
    "totalTime": 14490
  },
  {
    "question": "What does essence define?",
    "answer": "Essence defines the irreducible core nature of a thing.",
    "providedAnswer": "The fundamental nature of a thing. Its irreducable core that defindes it's identity. ",
    "totalTime": 50362,
    "clicks": 0,
    "clickedNodes": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What does essence define?",
    "answer": "Essence defines the irreducible core nature of a thing.",
    "providedAnswer": "Essence is the fundamental nature of a thing. ",
    "totalTime": 39325,
    "expandedNodesPerClick": [
      5,
      2,
      1
    ],
    "precisionPerClick": [],
    "recallPerClick": [],
    "precisionsPerClick": []
  },
  {
    "question": "How does morality relate to behavior?",
    "answer": "Morality pertains to principles concerning the distinction between right and wrong behavior.",
    "providedAnswer": "It is the distinction between good and bad behaviour",
    "totalTime": 51356,
    "expandedNodesPerClick": [
      5,
      2,
      1,
      2,
      1
    ],
    "precisionPerClick": [],
    "recallPerClick": [],
    "precisionsPerClick": []
  },
  {
    "question": "How is a collectivity formed?",
    "answer": "A collectivity is a group of individuals considered as a whole.",
    "providedAnswer": "Collectivity referes to a group of individuals considered as a whole. ",
    "totalTime": 154279,
    "expandedNodesPerClick": [
      5,
      2,
      1,
      2,
      1,
      5,
      2,
      1,
      4,
      0,
      2,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "precisionPerClick": [],
    "recallPerClick": [],
    "precisionsPerClick": []
  },
  {
    "question": "How is knowledge acquired according to cognition?",
    "answer": "Cognition is the mental process of acquiring knowledge and understanding through thought, experience, and the senses.",
    "providedAnswer": "Knowledge is understanding thorugh thought, experiences and the senses",
    "totalTime": 281731,
    "expandedNodesPerClick": [
      5,
      2,
      1,
      2,
      1,
      5,
      2,
      1,
      4,
      0,
      2,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      4,
      1,
      0,
      2,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      5,
      1
    ],
    "precisionPerClick": [],
    "recallPerClick": []
  },
  {
    "question": "What does essence define?",
    "answer": "Essence defines the irreducible core nature of a thing.",
    "providedAnswer": "hi",
    "totalTime": 3572,
    "expandedNodesPerClick": [],
    "precisionPerClick": [],
    "recallPerClick": []
  },
  {
    "question": "How does morality relate to behavior?",
    "answer": "Morality pertains to principles concerning the distinction between right and wrong behavior.",
    "providedAnswer": "hih",
    "totalTime": 10780,
    "expandedNodesPerClick": [],
    "precisionPerClick": [],
    "recallPerClick": []
  },
  {
    "question": "How is a collectivity formed?",
    "answer": "A collectivity is a group of individuals considered as a whole.",
    "providedAnswer": "hih",
    "totalTime": 66636,
    "expandedNodesPerClick": [],
    "precisionPerClick": [],
    "recallPerClick": []
  },
  {
    "question": "How is knowledge acquired according to cognition?",
    "answer": "Cognition is the mental process of acquiring knowledge and understanding through thought, experience, and the senses.",
    "providedAnswer": "through though, experience and the senses",
    "totalTime": 4537347,
    "expandedNodesPerClick": [
      5,
      2
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How is a pattern defined in terms of characteristics or events?",
    "answer": "A pattern is a recurring characteristic or event.",
    "providedAnswer": "A recurring characteristic or event. ",
    "totalTime": 140434,
    "expandedNodesPerClick": [
      5,
      2,
      2,
      1
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does essence define?",
    "answer": "Essence defines the irreducible core nature of a thing.",
    "providedAnswer": "The fundamental nature of a thing",
    "totalTime": 23341,
    "expandedNodesPerClick": [
      5,
      1
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How does morality relate to behavior?",
    "answer": "Morality pertains to principles concerning the distinction between right and wrong behavior.",
    "providedAnswer": "Morality is good or bad behaviour",
    "totalTime": 48929,
    "expandedNodesPerClick": [
      5,
      1,
      2,
      1
    ]
  }
]